# MOSTAPHA TAHA

Front-End Developer

Signalia   EGYPT	freelancing_messages@hotmail.c	l.com   mostapha-taha.vercel.app
+201099041827	github.com/M0staphaTaha	in linkedin.com/in/mostapha-taha-106018239

# **PROFILE INFO**

I am a computer science student self-taught front-end developer with a passion for learning and creating beautiful and user-friendly web applications. I have been working as a front-end developer for the past three years.

I am always looking for new ways to improve my skills and knowledge. I am an active member of the open-source community and contribute to several projects on GitHub. I also attend conferences and workshops to learn from other developers.

I am a hard worker and I am always willing to go the extra mile. I am also a team player and I enjoy collaborating with others

# **EXPERIENCE**

## **2023 - PRESENT**

**IEEE Obour Institutes** 

## **WEB Instructor**

- Instructed students on the fundamentals of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and responsive design for front-end development.
- Administered assessments to evaluate students' proficiency and comprehension of SEO concepts and practices.
- Designed and facilitated activities that enhanced students' communication and collaboration skills using GitHub as a team platform.
- I also Contributed to the development of the IEEE website using React as a member of a three-person team.

You can view the website [ieee-front-amr-hafeez.vercel.app].

#### **2023 - PRESENT**

**GDSC Obour Institutes** 

# **WEB Instructor**

- Instructed students on the fundamentals of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and responsive design for front-end development.
- Administered assessments to evaluate students' proficiency and comprehension of SEO concepts and practices.
- Designed and facilitated activities that enhanced students' communication and collaboration skills using GitHub as a team platform.
- One of the students' final projects was a gdsc website using only html and css m0staphataha.github.io/GDSC

#### 2024

 I created an introductory website for an educational platform EDUCRAFT educraft-stockfish.vercel.app

# **CERTIFICATES** —

Icpc Problem Solving Level 1,2,3

React Information Technology Institute (ITI)

Hacher Rank JavaScript

## **EDUCATION**

2021 - Present

# Obour Institutes &

Bachelor of computer science

# **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JS (ES6)
- TypeScript
- BootStrap
- TailwindCSS
- SCSS
- SEO
- Jest
- Responsive Design
- React.is
- Git | Github
- Problem Solving &
- Communication Skills

# LANGUAGES

- Arabic
- English